You know, I I'm I'm never really short
on words and I am right now. So, it's uh
it's tough, but this is sports and you
got to be able to deal with it. You guys
go ahead.
>> What did you tell the team after
>> that? You know, I I be honest, you know,
I
I I love this team and uh you know, I
wasn't ready to stop working with them.
Thought we had two more weeks together.
Um but I am really grateful for each of
those individuals and the collective.
It's as special of a group top to bottom
as I've ever been around. Um that's
coaches and players included and um
you know that's what sports sports you
know it it represents a lot of different
things. It's it's beautiful thing though
you know this this game has brought me
some of the most special relationships
that I'll cherish. That's what this team
has done and this was a special year and
I think it's hard to fathom that it's
over. Um it'll take some time but uh
nothing but gratitude. That's what I
want them to know.
>> Uh hindsight's
tough in a situation like this, but on
your last offensive possession, it
looked like you were running down and
about to call it.
>> I was I mean, we had our chances. You
know, I I thought about it and, you
know, didn't decide to do it. You know,
obviously it didn't work out for us, but
um you know, I thought our guys played
well. I thought we you know, there was a
lot of things that, you know, we got a
lot of what we wanted today. Felt really
good about the way that our guys
executed, you know, specifically on the
offensive side. And, you know, that was
a situation where we just kind of came
up short. They kind of lucked into
having two guys peel on Kiran right
there. I know that that can't be part of
their design. So, it's a fortuitous bust
by them. Um, but it was um, you know,
they're an excellent team and you don't
take away anything. You know, they they
they earn the win and uh, you know,
they're NFC champs for a reason.
>> Special teams, Sean, special teams has
been an issue this year. Um, just one
one error tonight.
>> Yeah, I know. It's it's tough, you know,
because X-Man has been so reliable, you
know, and he he bobbled the first one
and we were lucky to get back on it and
then that one it it was costly. Um I
love him. He's done a great job, you
know, and then obviously Kiren did a
nice job being able to field it from
that point on, but uh you know, that was
a tough one, you know, where we get a
great stop coming out of the second
half. Um you feel like you're going to
be able to get some good momentum and
then they score on the very first play
after we turn it back over to open it up
to an 11-point lead. I love the way that
offensively we went right down the field
in four plays. Um I just thought there
was a lot of resolve, a lot of
resilience from our group and and we
just came up short today.
>> Fourth and four at the six. You talk
about that play defer.
>> Yeah, I was just talking about it. You
know, you talking about the one where we
ended up coming up short. Yeah, I mean
we just, you know, they they were
bringing a zero. They ended up peeling
two guys. Can't imagine that's what they
were really trying to do. and um kind of
trying to move off schedule and um you
know I'll have to go back and look at it
but there was other opportunities on the
previous play that we you know could
have converted on that one too
>> your group since 22 and and coming back
and and putting this thing back
together. You guys have gotten a step
closer every single time.
>> How do you figure out the next step in
all of this?
>> Well, I mean I think you make a couple
plays tonight and we're talking about a
different thing. So I don't think it's
as simple as that. you start all over. I
mean, you know that. And um and that's
what's so hard because to get to these
positions, you know, I mean,
there is so much work. There's so much
time. Things have to go your way. You
have to stay healthy. It's a special
group. And so, um you don't it you know
this and I I know you know this. I'm not
minimizing the question. It it doesn't
work like that. You know, you got to
make these plays and you got to
capitalize on these opportunities when
you get the chances. And um you know,
Seattle was able to do that and we
weren't. but doesn't take away my love
and appreciation for this football team.
>> Last one,
>> Sean. Do you expect Matthew Stafford to
be back next season?
>> Yeah. I mean, that's I mean, if he if he
still wants to play, the hell kind of
question is that?
>> The answer. Yeah.
>> Uh, you have to ask him. I We've been
totally present. Um, he's I know that if
he wants to, he's still playing at a
pretty damn good clip. I mean, he's the
MVP of the league, and if he's not, you
know, I mean, I got respect for
everybody else, but this guy played at a
level that's just different. I
appreciate you guys this year. Thank
you.